statvoo.com 2014-07-12

# Privacy Policy > Statvoo.com | Advanced Realtime Website Analytics

Your privacy is of paramount importance to Statvoo. This policy applies to all products and services offered by Statvoo.

Information we gather from you:

  * Because the Statvoo Service houses your website statistics on our servers, you must join for a Statvoo account. The registration process asks for an email and a password. Additionally some personally identifiable information can also be including at a later stage.
  * When you log into the Service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * When you send email or other communication to Statvoo, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

Statvoo will not share your personal information without your consent or unless required by law.

By the nature of our Service, Statvoo will gather statistics about the usage of your website and store that information. Statvoo will not share your website statistics without your consent.

Statvoo only processes personal information for the purpose of providing, improving, ensuring the delivery of, and developing new services to users.

If Statvoo becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information such as the number of sites using Statvoo, for example. Such information does not identify you individually.

We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

This Privacy Policy applies to websites and services that are owned and operated by Statvoo. We do not exercise control over the sites that may be linked from our website. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

Statvoo may change its Privacy Policy from time to time and at Statvoo's sole discretion. However, your rights will not be reduced without your explicit consent.
